Guide to the Men's Basketball Game Film Collection, 1947-1996 UA.13.01.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Men's Basketball Game Films
  - Harvard, 1989 February 14
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 2, 1989 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2498)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 3, 1989 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2499)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 4, 1989 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2500)
  - Kansas, 1989 February 18
    Duke win; score: 102-77
    - Duke vs. Kansas: Reel 1, 1989 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2501)
    - Duke vs. Kansas: Reel 2, 1989 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2502)
    - Duke vs. Kansas: Reel 3, 1989 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2503)
    - Duke vs. Kansas: Reel 4, 1989 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2504)
  - Georgia Tech, 1989 February 20
    Duke win; score: 91-66
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1989 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2505)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1989 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2506)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1989 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2507)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 4, 1989 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2508)
  - NC State, 1989 February 23
    Duke win; score: 86-65
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1989 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2509)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1989 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2510)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1989 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2511)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1989 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2512)
  - Arizona, 1989 February 26
    Duke loss; score: 75-77
    - Duke vs. Arizona: Reel 1, 1989 February 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2513)
    - Duke vs. Arizona: Reel 2, 1989 February 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2514)
    - Duke vs. Arizona: Reel 3, 1989 February 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2515)
    - Duke vs. Arizona: Reel 4, 1989 February 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2516)
  - Clemson, 1989 March 01
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1989 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2517)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1989 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2518)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1989 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2519)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1989 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2520)
  - North Carolina, 1989 March 05
    Duke win; score: 88-86
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1989 March 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2521)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1989 March 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2522)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1989 March 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2523)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1989 March 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2524)
  - Wake Forest, 1989 March 10
    Duke win; score: 88-64; ACC Tournament, Atlanta, Ga.
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1989 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2525)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1989 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2526)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1989 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2527)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1989 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2528)
  - West Virginia, 1989 March 10
    Duke win; score: 70-63; NCAA Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 1, 1989 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2529)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 2, 1989 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2530)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 3, 1989 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2531)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 4, 1989 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2532)
  - Virginia, 1989 March 11
    Duke win; score: 69-58; ACC Tournament, Atlanta, Ga.
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1989 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2533)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1989 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2534)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1989 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2535)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1989 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2536)
  - North Carolina, 1989 March 12
    Duke loss; score: 74-77; ACC Tournament, Atlanta, Ga.
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1989 March 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2537)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1989 March 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2538)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1989 March 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2539)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1989 March 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2540)
  - South Carolina State, 1989 March 16
    Duke win; score: 90-69; NCAA Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. South Carolina State: Reel 1, 1989 March 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2541)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina State: Reel 2, 1989 March 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2542)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina State: Reel 3, 1989 March 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2543)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina State: Reel 4, 1989 March 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2544)
  - Minnesota, 1989 March 24
    Duke win; score: 87-70; NCAA Tournament, East Rutherford, NJ
    - Duke vs. Minnesota: Reel 1, 1989 March 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2545)
    - Duke vs. Minnesota: Reel 2, 1989 March 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2546)
    - Duke vs. Minnesota: Reel 3, 1989 March 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2547)
    - Duke vs. Minnesota: Reel 4, 1989 March 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2548)
  - Georgetown, 1989 March 26
    Duke win; score: 85-77; NCAA Tournament, East Rutherford, NJ
    - Duke vs. Georgetown: Reel 1, 1989 March 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2549)
    - Duke vs. Georgetown: Reel 2, 1989 March 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2550)
    - Duke vs. Georgetown: Reel 3, 1989 March 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2551)
    - Duke vs. Georgetown: Reel 4, 1989 March 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2552)
  - AAU High Fives, 1989 November 11
    - AAU High Fives: Reel 1, 1989 November 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2553)
    - AAU High Fives: Reel 2, 1989 November 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2554)
    - AAU High Fives: Reel 3, 1989 November 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2555)
  - Harvard, 1989 November 25
    Duke win; score: 103-54
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 1, 1989 November 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2556)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 2, 1989 November 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2557)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 3, 1989 November 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2558)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 4, 1989 November 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2559)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 5, 1989 November 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2560)
  - Canisius, 1989 November 29
    Duke win; score: 102-66
    - Duke vs. Canisius: Reel 1, 1989 November 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2561)
    - Duke vs. Canisius: Reel 2, 1989 November 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2562)
    - Duke vs. Canisius: Reel 3, 1989 November 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2563)
    - Duke vs. Canisius: Reel 4, 1989 November 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2564)
  - Northwestern, 1989 December 02
    Duke win; score: 103-77
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 1, 1989 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2565)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 2, 1989 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2566)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 3, 1989 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2567)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 4, 1989 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2568)
  - Syracuse, 1989 December 06
    Duke loss; score: 76-78; ACC/Big East Challenge, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Syracuse: Reel 1, 1989 December 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2569)
    - Duke vs. Syracuse: Reel 2, 1989 December 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2570)
    - Duke vs. Syracuse: Reel 3, 1989 December 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2571)
    - Duke vs. Syracuse: Reel 4, 1989 December 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2572)
  - Michigan, 1989 December 09
    Duke loss; score: 108-113
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 1, 1989 December 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2573)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 2, 1989 December 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2574)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 3, 1989 December 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2575)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 4, 1989 December 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2576)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 5, 1989 December 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2577)
  - Davidson, 1989 December 21
    Duke win; score: 89-44
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 1, 1989 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2578)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 2, 1989 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2579)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 3, 1989 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2580)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 4, 1989 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2581)
  - Washington, 1989 December 23
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 1, 1989 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2582)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 2, 1989 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2583)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 3, 1989 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2584)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 4, 1989 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2585)
  - Drake, 1989 December 28
    Duke win; score: 101-77; Rainbow Classic, Honolulu, Hawaii
    - Duke vs. Drake: Reel 1, 1989 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2586)
    - Duke vs. Drake: Reel 2, 1989 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2587)
    - Duke vs. Drake: Reel 3, 1989 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2588)
    - Duke vs. Drake: Reel 4, 1989 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2589)
    - Duke vs. Drake: Reel 5, 1989 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2590)
  - Cincinnati, 1989 December 29
    Duke win; score: 95-83; Rainbow Classic, Honolulu, Hawaii
    - Duke vs. Cincinnati: Reel 1, 1989 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2591)
    - Duke vs. Cincinnati: Reel 2, 1989 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2592)
    - Duke vs. Cincinnati: Reel 3, 1989 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2593)
    - Duke vs. Cincinnati: Reel 4, 1989 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2594)
    - Duke vs. Cincinnati: Reel 5, 1989 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2595)
  - Hawaii, 1989 December 30
    Duke win; score: 87-75; Rainbow Classic, Honolulu, Hawaii
    - Duke vs. Hawaii: Reel 1, 1989 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2596)
    - Duke vs. Hawaii: Reel 2, 1989 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2597)
    - Duke vs. Hawaii: Reel 3, 1989 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2598)
    - Duke vs. Hawaii: Reel 4, 1989 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2599)
    - Duke vs. Hawaii: Reel 5, 1989 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2600)
  - Citadel, 1990 January 03
    Duke win; score: 108-69
    - Duke vs. Citadel: Reel 1, 1990 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2601)
    - Duke vs. Citadel: Reel 2, 1990 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2602)
    - Duke vs. Citadel: Reel 3, 1990 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2603)
    - Duke vs. Citadel: Reel 4, 1990 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2604)
  - Georgia Tech, 1990 January 11
    Duke win; score: 96-91
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1990 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2605)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1990 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2606)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1990 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2607)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 4, 1990 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2608)
  - Maryland, 1990 January 13
    Duke win; score: 91-80
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1990 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2609)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1990 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2610)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1990 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2611)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1990 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2612)
  - North Carolina, 1990 January 17
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1990 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2613)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1990 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2614)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1990 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2615)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1990 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2616)
  - Wake Forest, 1990 January 20
    Duke win; score: 97-69
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1990 January 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2617)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1990 January 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2618)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1990 January 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2619)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1990 January 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2620)
  - William & Mary, 1990 January 22
    Duke win; score: 109-76
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 1, 1990 January 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2621)
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 2, 1990 January 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2622)
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 3, 1990 January 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2623)
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 4, 1990 January 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2624)
  - NC State, 1990 January 24
    Duke win; score: 85-82
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1990 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2625)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1990 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2626)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1990 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2627)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1990 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2628)
  - Georgia Tech, 1990 January 28
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1990 January 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2629)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1990 January 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2630)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1990 January 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2631)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 4, 1990 January 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2632)
  - Clemson, 1990 January 31
    Duke win; score: 94-80
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1990 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2633)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1990 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2634)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1990 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2635)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1990 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2636)
  - Notre Dame, 1990 February 04
    Duke win; score: 88-76
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 1, 1990 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2637)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 2, 1990 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2638)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 3, 1990 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2639)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 4, 1990 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2640)
  - Virginia, 1990 February 08
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1990 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2641)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1990 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2642)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1990 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2643)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1990 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2644)
  - Maryland, 1990 February 10
    Duke win; score: 114-111
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1990 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2645)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1990 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2646)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1990 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2647)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1990 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2648)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 5, 1990 February 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2649)
  - Stetson, 1990 February 12
    Duke win; score: 102-67
    - Duke vs. Stetson: Reel 1, 1990 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2650)
    - Duke vs. Stetson: Reel 2, 1990 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2651)
    - Duke vs. Stetson: Reel 3, 1990 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2652)
    - Duke vs. Stetson: Reel 4, 1990 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2653)
  - East Carolina, 1990 February 14
    Duke win; score: 84-51
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 1, 1990 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2654)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 2, 1990 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2655)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 3, 1990 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2656)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 4, 1990 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2657)
  - Wake Forest, 1990 February 18
    Duke win; score: 71-56
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1990 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2658)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1990 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2659)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1990 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2660)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1990 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2661)
  - NC State, 1990 February 21
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1990 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2662)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1990 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2663)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1990 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2664)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1990 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2665)
  - Arizona, 1990 February 25
    Duke win; score: 78-76
    - Duke vs. Arizona: Reel 1, 1990 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2666)
    - Duke vs. Arizona: Reel 2, 1990 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2667)
    - Duke vs. Arizona: Reel 3, 1990 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2668)
    - Duke vs. Arizona: Reel 4, 1990 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2669)
  - Clemson, 1990 February 28
    Duke loss; score: 93-97
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1990 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2670)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1990 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2671)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1990 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2672)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1990 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2673)
  - North Carolina, 1990 March 04
    Duke loss; score: 75-87
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1990 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2674)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1990 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2675)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1990 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2676)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1990 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2677)
  - Maryland, 1990 March 09
    Duke win; score: 104-84; ACC Tournament, Charlotte, NC
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1990 March 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 118, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2678)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1990 March 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 118, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2679)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1990 March 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 118, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2680)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1990 March 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 118, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2681)
  - Georgia Tech, 1990 March 10
    Duke loss; score: 72-83; ACC Tournament, Charlotte, NC
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1990 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2682)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1990 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 117, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2683)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1990 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 118, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2684)